{
    "subject": "resource/Nia_Long",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Brooklyn",
    "human_readable": "Nia Long was born in Brooklyn.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8139175772666931,
            "question": "Where was Nia Long born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5936878323554993,
            "question": "Where did Nia Long grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4068484604358673,
            "question": "What is Nia Long known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.273211807012558,
            "question": "Has Nia Long been involved in any philanthropic work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24178731441497803,
            "question": "Is there anything else noteworthy about Nia Long's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23507095873355865,
            "question": "In what films has Nia Long appeared?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21693694591522217,
            "question": "Who are some of Nia Long's notable co-stars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20439301431179047,
            "question": "Is Nia Long an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19064198434352875,
            "question": "Has Nia Long won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11234453320503235,
            "question": "What type of roles is Nia Long often cast in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nia Long was born in Brooklyn.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7726_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Nia Long won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7726_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Nia Long an actress?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7726_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of Nia Long's notable co-stars?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7726_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7726_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response to your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all of the documents mention that Nia Long was born in Brooklyn, New York."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents explicitly state that Nia Long was born in Brooklyn, New York. Therefore, the statement \"Nia Long was born in Brooklyn\" is correct according to the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}